{
  "extraDescription": "for cubes of 0-10 and roots in 0-10",
  "randomQuestionCount": 3,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "2&sup3;",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "7&sup3;",
      "answer": "343"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt[3]{125}\\)",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "4&sup3;",
      "answer": "64"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt[3]{8}\\)",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "5&sup3;",
      "answer": "125"
    },
    {
      "question": "0&sup3;",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "6&sup3;",
      "answer": "216"
    },
    {
      "question": "1&sup3;",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt[3]{729}\\)",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt[3]{1000}\\)",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt[3]{64}\\)",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt[3]{512}\\)",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "10&sup3;",
      "answer": "1000"
    },
    {
      "question": "9&sup3;",
      "answer": "729"
    },
    {
      "question": "8&sup3;",
      "answer": "512"
    },
    {
      "question": "3&sup3;",
      "answer": "27"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt[3]{343}\\)",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt[3]{27}\\)",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt[3]{0}\\)",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt[3]{1}\\)",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt[3]{216}\\)",
      "answer": "6"
    }
  ]
}
